Guide to the Community Service Society Archives
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XVI: Historical Data, 1970 & Following
  - Subseries XVI.1: Historical Data
    - Small Claims Court Consumer Judgments, A Proposal to increase the collectability of Better Business Bureau of Metropolitan New York, Inc. 1976 (Box 508)
    - Social Casework - see: Bulletin 616, March 1961 (Box 508)
    - Social Issues (Box 508)
    - Social Security Act (Box 508)
    - Social Work Education and Practice - A Proposed Center to Advance their Relationship 1979 (Box 508)
    - Social Workers' Roles (Box 508)
    - South Brooklyn Alternative Education Program Proposed (Box 508)
    - Southeast Bronx Family Service (a.k.a. "Longwood North") (Box 508)
    - Staff Development (Box 508)
    - Staff: Job Descriptions 1978 (Box 508)
    - Staff: Miscellaneous:
      - Memos To, From and Re (Box 508)
      - Meetings, General (Box 509)
      - Meetings, Executive (Box 509)
    - Staff Salaries, Loans - see: Salaries (Box 509)
    - Staff Seminar "Shared Power" 1974-1975 (Box 509)
    - State Constitution - Amendment Proposed 1977 (Box 509)
    - Statistics - Monthly Service Records:
      - Examples: September, July 1977 (Box 509)
      - Examples: January 1976 (Box 509)
      - Examples: January 1975 (Box 509)
    - Structure and Function of CSS - Beck, Comments (full document in Reports) to Trustees, 1978 (Box 509)
    - Students (Box 509)
    - Studies (Internal) and Reorganizations (Also in Reports: Study Committee) (Box 509)
    - Supplemental Security Income (SSI) - Adjustments to the new Federal Assistance Program 9/1973-10/1976 (Note: Contains Confidential Material) (Box 509)
    - Survey of Poor (People's Opinions) in South Bronx (Box 510)
    - Survival Issues Committees (Box 510)
    - Union for Staff (Box 510)
    - United Charities Building (Box 510)
    - U.S. Budget: Campaign to oppose budget cutting proposed in US President's Budget 4/28/1981 (Box 511)
    - Vacation Services: Restricted Funds (Camp Fund) (Box 511)
    - Volunteer Service (Box 511)
    - Ward Manor 1977-1980 (Box 511)
    - Property (cemetery diagram is with Corporate Assistant H. Dogue) (Box 511)
    - Ward Manor Residents 1958 (Box 511)
    - Welfare Cost Stabilization - A Proposal, 1975 by Alvin Schorr et al (Box 511)
    - Welfare Moving Expenses see: Public Assistance (Box 511)
    - Welfare Reform Task Force (Box 511)
    - Williams, H.K.S., Trust II 1970 (received through N.Y. Community Trust) (Box 511)
    - Work Environment Committee and Management Committee (Box 511)
    - Youth and Correction, etc., Miscellaneous 1970-1977 ff (later: Committee on Criminal and Juvenile Justice) (Box 511)
    - Youth Board (reports to Re: Services for Children, etc. (Box 511)
  - Subseries XVI.2:Reports, Pamphlets, Clippings
    - "ABOUT CSS" - Staff Newsletter Fall 1975 - May-June 1981 (Box 512)
    - Adolescent Girls, Concerns Of - Committee on Health See Concerns of... (Box 512)
    - "Aging" March-April 1979, 1976 - contains 4 pieces describing CSS programs in the field (See Also Author Listings) (Box 512)
    - Aging - Annual Legislative Reports (Samples ) (Box 512)
    - Aging, Caring For The ...4 Handbooks by Natural Support Committee:
      - Helping Older People, an Information Directory (Box 512)
      - Helping Older People, Staten Island (Box 512)
      - Helping Your Older Relatives, with Lenox Hill, Hartley House and Staten Island Interagency Council on Aging (Box 512)
    - Aging, Committee on, Minutes - 1970 ff (Folder 1) (Box 512)
    - Aging, Committee on, Minutes - 1970 ff (Folders 2-4 ) (Box 513)
    - Aging, Conservatorship Colloquium (Box 513)
    - Aging - Mary Zander papers given at Gerontological Society 1977 (Box 513)
    - Aging: Toward Income Adequacy for the Elderly implication s of the SSI Program for New York City Residents, ISWR 1982 (Box 513)
    - All In The Family - House Organ - April, September 1979 (Box 513)
    - Alternative Management Programs: A Housing Resource Guide 1980 (Box 513)
    - Amicus, Financial Guide 1978-79 (Box 513)
    - Anniversary, Hundredth: (Box 514)
      - Papers of the Community Service Society of New York (Box 514)
      - Papers of the New York School of Social Work (See: Family in a Democratic Society and Social Work as Human Relations (Box 514)
    - Anniversary, 125th Observance, October 1974 - 7 papers, 107 pp. by Myrdals et al (Box 514)
    - Another Choice/Another Chance - A Survey of Alternative Public High School Programs in New York City, Department of Public Affairs, October 1976 for Committee on Education by Jo LoCicero Consultant for Education, October 197 6 4 3 pp. and appendix $1.50 (Box 514)
    - Applying For Public Assistance In New York City by Project Access 1977 (Box 514)
    - Archives Committee - Minutes 10/29/79 (Box 514)
    - Archives Lists (Genera l Director has one set) (Box 514)
    - Assessment Of Staff Development Needs Within Community Service Society by Shirley Bryant, Draft 4/15/77 and related memos a.k.a. "Bryant Report" (also with General file "Staff Development") (Box 514)
    - Beck, Bertram - Papers: (Box 514)
    - The Lower East Side Family Union: A Social Intervention Comprehensive Services for Families and Children in the United States, ca. 1980 (an occasional paper for the Foundation for Child Development 3/79) (Box 514)
    - Youth Within Walls (Box 514)
    - Big Flat, The - History of a NY Tenement House by Robert H. Bremner, October 1958 8 pp. (Box 514)
    - Bilingual Education, Studies 1974 & 1975 (Box 514)
    - "Bryant Report" - See Staff (Box 515)
    - Budget Of New York City - Monitoring NYC's Budget and Preserving the Democratic Process, Levy & Feinstein 1977 (Box 515)
    - Burns, Eveline M. - "Social Welfare in the 1980s and Beyond" 6/2/77, 20 pp. (Box 515)
    - By-Laws 1980, 1967 (Box 515)
    - Captive Consumer, 1975 - Prescription Drugs & Consumer Rights (Box 515)
    - Consumers Guide To Health Resources - Lower West Side 1978 (Box 515)
    - Caregivers Make The Difference - Group Services for Those Caring for Older Persons in the Community, The Natural Supports Program, Anna H. Zimmer, M. Joanna Mellor 9/81 (Box 515)
    - Caregivers Of The Aged, Support Groups For - A Training Manual for Facilitators 1981 (Box 515)
    - "CASC" - Community Agency for Senior Citizens of Staten Island Minutes (Box 515)
    - CACS News 1978-80 (Box 515)
    - Central Services & Family Services, Reports for CSS Study 1970 (Box 515)
    - The Changing Face Of Poverty, Trends in New York City's Population in Poverty 1960-1990 by Emanuel Tobler, New York University 11/84 for CSS (Box 515)
    - Chasing The American Dream - Jobs, Schools & Employment Training Programs in New York State - CSS with New York State Conference of NAACP 11/80 (Box 516)
    - Child Protective Services Act Of 1973 A Study of the Effects of The, in 17 counties of New York State - 7/75 (Box 516)
    - Child Watch: New York City - report of the New York City Monitoring Project by Eleanor Marshall & Anjean Carter March 1983 30 pp. (Box 516)
    - Chinatown - Dunham Report "On Growth & Development of CSS PHN Service in Chinatown 1944-53" (second copy - original at Columbia), Bulletins 1971 & 1972 Pamphlet 1968-70 (Box 516)
    - Chinatown Health & Service Center: Program Review 1976 (Box 516)
    - Chinatown, Mental Health Programming For, Issues & Options Joan Schilt, 1977 (Box 516)
    - Chinatown, Planning for Schilt Report (Box 516)
    - Chinese Americans, Use Of Neighborhood Health Services by Taran, 1976 (Box 516)
    - Civil Disabilities - Information Paper for Committee on Youth and Correction by Carol Whelan 1973 (Box 516)
    - Closed Labor Market: Under representation of Blacks, Hispanics & Women in New York City's Core Industries & Jobs by Walter M. Stafford, Fellow in Employment & Economic Development, January 1985 205 pp. (Box 516)
    - Committees - Post 1970 (Box 517)
      - Aging (special) (Box 517)
      - Chinatown (Box 517)
      - Criminal & Juvenile Justice (Box 517)
      - Education (Box 517)
      - Executive (Box 517)
      - Family and Child Welfare (Box 517)
      - General Program & Issues (Box 517)
      - Health and Nutrition (Box 517)
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 517)
      - Income Maintenance (Box 517)
      - Job and Economic Development (Box 518)
      - Security of the Person (Box 518)
      - Social Services (Box 518)
    - Survival Issues (Box 518)
    - Community Boards, Guide & Check List (Box 518)
    - Community Board Project To Implement Charter Revision, Miles with Feinman 1976 (Box 518)
    - Community Care Facilities, Planned Placement Of, 1978 (Box 518)
    - Community Care Programs For The Frail Elderly - Based on Symposium 10/10/75 102 pp. (Box 518)
    - Community, Department For: (Box 518)
    - "The Targeting of CSS Training and Technical Assistance Services Towards the Critical Areas of NYC" by James P. Fogerty et al (Box 518)
    - Other Pamphlets (Box 518)
    - Concerns Of Adolescent Girls - Committees on Health and on Family Life Education, April 1968 21 pp. (Box 518)
    - Consumer Advisory Council 1977 (Box 518)
    - Consumer Protection, Special Committee on - Minutes 1972 (Box 518)
    - Consumer Credit (Box 518)
    - Corporate Directory 1985-86: Lists officers, trustees, meeting schedule; committee, commission and task force membership. Includes By-Laws to 1982 (Box 518)
    - Correctional Programs, Community Oriented - Committee on Youth & Correction, 1975 (Box 518)
    - Council For Interdepartmental Communications - Minutes 1971-72 (Box 519)
    - Courts & Correction - Statements 1976-77 (Box 519)
    - Credit Unions - Technical Assistance, Ellen Lurie 1975 (Box 519)
    - "Crime Against The Elderly" - Personal Safety Sub-committee on Aging, 6/76 30 pp. (Box 519)
    - Criminal & Juvenile Justice Committee (formerly Youth & Correction) See Committee (Box 519)
    - CSS News, CSS People, 1983-84 (also CSS in the News 1982) - House Organs (Box 519)
    - Day Care, The Decline Of, In New York City 1977 (Box 519)
    - Decline Of Day Care Services And Its Impact On New York City Families 1976 (Box 519)
    - Day Care And The Working Poor, the Struggle for Self - Sufficiency by Georgia L. McMurray and Dolores O. Kazanjian 1982 (Box 519)
    - Delivery Of Health Services In A Senior Center Designed For The Mentally Frail Elderly: An Evaluation, 1976 by Ruth Goldman (Box 519)
    - Demographic Analysis: Community Planning Board #1 - Bronx (South) for CSS by Mobicentrics 1976 (Box 520)
    - Departmental Reports, Abstracts For Board Study Committee 1970
      - Central Services Department Report for Study 1970 and Family Services Department Report for Study 1970 (Box 520)
      - Welfare Research Institute, Personnel Department and Personnel Practices, Report for Study 1970 (Box 520)
      - Public Relations Department and Fund Raising Department, Reports for Study 1970 (Box 520)
      - Task Force on Continuing Programs, 1979 Report to Executive Committee on Department of Family & Individual Well-Being (Box 520)
    - Detention, The Case For Alternatives To by Edward Pabon, ACSW 1981 (Box 520)
    - Drug Abusers, Treatment Programs For New York City's Youthful:
      - Part I 197 2 (Box 520)
      - Part II 1974 (Box 520)
    - "Dynamic Approaches To Serving Families," 1970 (Box 520)
    - Education - Bilingual & Handicapped (Box 520)
    - Education Committee - Minutes & Statements 1977-81 (Folders 1 & 2) (Box 520)
    - Education Committee - Minutes & Statements 1977-81 (Folder 3) (Box 521)
    - Education For Expectant Parents, Directory Of (NYC, Nassau Westchester) 1972 57 pp. $1.00 (Box 521)
    - Elderly Crime Victims Assistance Programs, Pilot Project 4/78 6/79, 33 pp. (Box 521)
    - Evaluative Researchers And Practitioners: Conflicts & Accommodation Frank G. Caro in Journal of Research & Development in Education, Vol. 8, No. 3, 1975 (Box 521)
    - Executive Cabinet, Minutes (Box 521)
    - Executive Committee - Minutes (Box 521)
    - Executive Committee For Planning Task Force, Minutes and Continuing Programs (Box 521)
    - The Family Agency, Liberty, Government And by Alvin L. Schorr, Social Casework 3/74, 5 pp. (Box 521)
    - (The) Family As An Informal Support To The Elderly - an annotated bibliography, 1977 (Box 521)
    - Family Care Of The Elderly-Frankfather, Smith, Caro -1981 ? 175 pp. (Box 521)
    - (The) Family In a Democratic Society, 1949. 287 pages (Box 521)
    - Family Court/Mental Health Background Information: Three Papers by Ed Pabon 4/24/78 (Box 521)
    - Family Financial Counseling, Guide For by Edith Taihonen, Home Economics Consultant, Public Affairs Department, 1972 (Box 521)
    - Family & Individual Well-Being Department, Report of Task Force on Continuing Programs, 63 pp. 4/79 (Box 521)
    - Family Life Education, 3 Reports: (Box 522)
      - Young Families Project, 1971 (Box 522)
      - Life in Public Housing, 1971 (Box 522)
      - The Haitian Family, 1970 (Box 522)
    - Family Services:
      - Family Counseling Services in New York City - Report to Committee on Public Affairs by Forrest Whitney 1/15/75 (Box 522)
      - A Proposal for a Family & Children's Center by Leyendecker & Whitney 1/28/75 (Box 522)
    - Family Services Committee, Minutes 1971 (Box 522)
    - Federal Budget Process, Status Report On, 11/22/82 (Box 522)
    - Finance Committee – Minutes (Box 522)
    - Financial Accountants Reports 1961-1971, 1983 (Box 522)
    - Financial Management Issues And Reporting Requirements Of South Bronx Community Organizations. Problems & Recommendations by Herzog & Kirschner 1981 (Box 522)
    - Finance and Real Estate Committee - Minutes 1971-76 (Box 522)
    - Five States: A Study of the Youth Authority Program, July 1951 by Bert Beck for American Law Institute (Box 522)
    - Friday Memo from the General Director July 1981 ff etc. by B. Beck 1/3/83-7/23/8 4 (Box 522)
    - Frontiers In Human Welfare, 1948 84 pages (Box 522)
    - Fund Raising v. Report from Department o f Fund Raising to Study Committee (Box 523)
    - General Programs and Issues Committee (Box 523)
    - General Reports (Box 523)
    - Gatekeeping Study 1977 M. Fabricant (see: Family Court) (Box 523)
    - Goldberg, Gertrude S. - Dissertation 1975 New Directions for the CSS of New York, A Study of Organizational Change (Chapters IVI and VI-XII) also Xerox copy and comment (Box 523)
    - Government Policies Affecting Children & Families by Georgia L. McMurray, 1977 (Box 523)
    - Guide For Family Financial Counseling by Edith Taittonen, Home Economics Consultant 1972 (Box 523)
    - Guideposts: 2nd Century of Community Service (Box 523)
    - Guides For Public Health Nurses see: Family Health Series (Box 523)
    - Haitian Family, The for Committee on Family Life Education by Ketty Hippolyte Rey 197 0 $1.00 - 37 pp. and appendix (Box 523)
    - Hardship In The Heartland: Homelessness in Eight U.S. Cities by Dan Salerno, Kim Hopper & Ellen Baxter of ISWR, 184 pp., 1984 (Box 523)
    - Health & Nutrition Committee, Minutes 1978-81 (Box 523)
    - Helping Older People: An Information Directory for Concerned Relatives, Friends & Neighbors of the Aging & Special Sections on Clinton, Harlem, Upper West Side, Upper East Side, Queens, Staten Island (*Spanish Version includes all above) *"Audando A Personas Ansianas" by Natural Supports Program 9/81 (Box 524)
    - "Helping Your Older Relatives" - A Guidebook by Natural Supports Program with Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association 1981 (Box 524)
    - History Of CSS - Manuscript by Sallie E. Bright, unfinished (written in the 70's)
      - Part I 12 3 pp. (Box 524)
      - Part II 124-20 8 pp. (Box 524)
      - Part III & illustrations (miscellaneous segments) (Box 524)
    - History of CSS, Oral, 1981 (Filed in Columbia Oral History Collection)
      - Reminiscences of Clare M. Tousley 26 0 pp. 198 1 (Box 524)
      - Reminiscences of Ollie A, Randall 5 3 pp. 1981 (Box 524)
      - Reminiscences of Stanley Davies, 141 pp. 1981 (Box 524)
    - History of CSS - 2 pamphlets: Robert d e Forest, Josephine Sha w Lowell (Box 525)
    - Home Economics: Guide for Family Financial Counseling, Taittonen, Home Economics Consultant 1972 (Box 525)
    - Homeless Youth In New York City: A field study by Theodore G. Hackman, MSW, assisted by John L. Cooper, Ph.D. April 1977 $2.00, 63 pp. (Box 525)
    - (How) Homemaker Service Met Medical Needs - CSS Hospital Homemaker (Box 525)
    - Home Health Aide Study, Powers et al 1971 (Box 525)
    - House Organs - Miscellaneous: Community Board Project News, Research Utilization Newsletter, Volunteers, a Newsletter for (also see "Friday Memo," "Memo to Members," "People") (Box 525)
    - Housing: Code Enforcement And Housing Maintenance In New York City 1972 - Committee on Housing and Urban Development 9 8 pp. (Box 525)
    - Housing Computer Link Evaluation 1976 (Box 525)
    - Housing - Fifty Years Of Action...Hill (Box 525)
    - Housing, Life In Public, Equals Tenants Plus Management - A 6 year Demonstration, 1971 see Life in Public Housing (Box 525)
    - Housing And Urban Development, Committee on Minutes 1971-81:
      - Report on In-Rem Task Force 1981 - Housing & Urban Development 12/29/80 (Box 525)
      - Legislation in New York State 1973-74 (Box 526)
    - Housing: Reforming The Community Development Program 1979 (See Reforming the Community Development Program) (Box 526)
    - Income Maintenance Committee - Minutes and Statements 1979-1981 (Box 526)
    - Income Security Committee: "Carter's Welfare Reform, an Overview" by Maureen Lally 1977 (Box 527)
    - Informal Child Care, A study of (with emphasis on the South Bronx) by "Mobicentrics" for CSS 1976 (Box 527)
    - Information Needs And Information Patterns - Unsigned but said to be by Braverman (probably 1981) (Box 527)
    - Jobs And Economic Development Committee - Minutes 1980-1981 (Box 527)
    - Junior Committee 1970-71 (Box 527)
    - Juvenile Injustice: Dilemmas Of The Family Court System 198 pp., 1981 ISWR (Box 527)
    - Juvenile Mediation And Family Arbitration, Minutes and Reports of (Box 527)
    - Committee on Juvenile Justice etc. (Box 527)
    - Large Grievances About Small Causes 1974 (Box 527)
    - Lawyers Committee Minutes & Memos 10-12/76 (Box 527)
    - Legislative Priorities 1978 Highlights 1977 (Box 527)
    - Legislative Reports - Sample, 197 6 (Box 527)
    - Letter To Jeanie, with love, CMT by Clare M. Tousley 1974 70 pp. (Box 528)
    - Life In Public Housing (Box 528)
    - Life In Public Housing Equals Tenants Plus Management, Committee on Family Life Education, Alexander Greendale 404 pp. 1971 (Box 528)
    - Lowell, Josephine Shaw 1843-1905 A Volunteer in Social Work by Margaret Rich, 1954 CSS (Box 528)
    - (The) Making Of America's Homeless: From Skid Row To New Poor, 1945-84 by Kim Hopper and Jill Hamberg (Box 528)
    - Making The Punishment Fit The Crime: A Proposal for Determinate\Sentences for Juveniles 1976 - Committee on Criminal and ' Juvenile Justice Mandatory Retirement, 197 9 (Box 528)
    - Mapping OF Selected Problems and Population Characteristics In New York City by E.L. Lyman, A.S. Stumson, J.B. Stimson, IWR 1971 (Box 528)
    - Marijuana, The Non-Narcotic Dangerous Drug - Committee on Youth & Correction 1970 (Box 528)
    - Medical Care Prices & The Consumer Price Index 1973 by Ellenbogen, Gladys, Ph.D. (Box 528)
    - Mentally Disabled Adults In Community Settings, Quality Of Life Of by Ellen Baxter & Kim Hopper 9/792 4 pp. (Box 528)
    - Methadone Maintenance Treatment in New York City, Committee on Youth & Correction 1975 76 pp. (Folder 1) (Box 528)
    - Methadone Maintenance Treatment In New York City, Committee on Youth & Correction 1975 76 pp. Folder 2 (Box 529)
    - Method And Progress In Social Casework Minority Enterprise Small Business Investment Corp ("MESBIC") Report 1982 by Agustin Rivera (Box 529)
    - Narcotics:
      - Treatment Programs (Box 529)
      - Methadone Maintenance see Methadone Maintenance (Box 529)
      - Observations of 5 Residential Facilities of Narcotic Addiction Control Committee (Box 529)
      - Marijuana see Marijuana (Box 529)
    - National Health Insurance: Toward Quality Care All Can Afford 1975 Committee Statement 1972 (Box 529)
    - Natural Supports Program 1976-81:
      - Group Services for Those Caring for Older Persons in the Community (Box 529)
      - Helping Your Older Relatives - A Guidebook (Box 529)
      - Training Manual, etc. (Box 529)
      - Gerontology Society Papers 1980 (Box 529)
      - Network News May 1980 (Box 529)
      - List of Publications (Box 529)
    - "Neighborhood Service Delivery", 3 papers 1974 by Jacqueline Ancelin, Eugene Litwak, Vitomer Stojakovic (Box 529)
    - New York City Taxes and Expenditures, The Burden Of, Committee on Income Security 1976 (Box 529)
    - New York City's Municipal Hospital System...Comments & Recommendations by Task Force, 1979 (Box 529)
    - New York City's 19th Century Child Welfare System...As it Operates in 1975 A Study of (Unsigned Draft 9/12/75) (Box 529)
    - News, In The:
      - Winter 1983 Selected Publicity (Box 529)
      - Summer 1983 Selected Publicity (Box 529)
      - 1984-85 (Box 529)
    - Newsletter, Vol. 1, No. 1, Summer 1983 (Box 530)
    - Nominating Committee Minute s 1976, 1978, 1984 (Box 530)
    - Nutrition Leaflets For Chinatown et al 1970 ff (Box 530)
    - Old Age Security And The Problems Of Oasdi - Part I by Eveline M. Burns, Consultant 1976 (Box 530)
    - Older Relatives, Helping Your - A Guidebook, Natural Supports 1981 (Box 530)
    - One Year Later, The Homeless Poor in New York City, 1982 by Hopper, Baxter, Cox an d Klein 6/82 (Box 530)
    - Opportunity Shop - Minutes 1972, 1970, 1969 (Box 530)
    - Pamphlets General an d Miscellaneous from 1942 (Box 530)
    - Pamphlets "Facts" about CSS 1962-67, 1969 (Box 530)
    - Pamphlets Promotional 7 Descriptive, 1970 ff (Box 530)
    - Parent Locator and Support Program (Box 530)
    - Publications - Internal:
      - About CSS (Box 530)
      - Campaign News (Box 530)
      - Friday Memo (Box 530)
      - House Organs (Miscellaneous) (Box 530)
      - JSPOA Newsletter (Box 530)
      - Memo to Members (Box 530)
      - RSVP/SERVE Newsletter (Box 530)
      - What's Going On (Box 530)
      - People (Successor to "In the News") (Box 530)
    - Personnel Practices Manual, 1975 (Box 530)
    - Photos (Box 530)
    - Planned Placement Of Community Care Facilities - 1978 (Box 530)
    - Planning Committee - Minutes & Reports 1981 (Box 531)
    - Research Committee of the Board - Minutes 5/73-5/77 (Box 531)
    - Poverty, The Changing Face of - Trends in New York City Population 1960-90 by Emanuel Tobier, NYU, 11/84 for CSS 43 PP. (Box 531)
    - Prescription Drugs see The Captive Consumer (Box 531)
    - Prison Health Care in New York City - A Historical Perspective Medvene (Student) and Whelan 1976 26 pp. (Box 531)
    - Prison Reform, Where Do You Stand? 1973-7 4 (Box 531)
    - Private Lives/Public Spaces, Homeless Adults on the Streets of New York City by Ellen Baxter and Kim Hunter, ISWR February 1981 - Report and News Clippings and Sequel One Year Later, The Homeless Poor in New York City, 1982 121 pp. (Box 531)
    - Private Pension Legislation, Review and Recommendations 1973 \ Committee on Aging of Department of Public Affairs by Gladys Ellenbogen, Ph.D. (Box 531)
    - Program Proposed 1978-79 (Box 532)
    - Program Agenda 1983/84, March 1984, 1973, 1978 (Box 532)
    - Program Staff Planning Committee - Minutes 6/2/76-9/30/76 (Box 532)
    - Progress Notes, CSS 1981, 1980 (Box 532)
    - Prospective Reimbursements for Hospitals, A Guide for Policy Makers by Laudicina, S.S., for Committee on Health 1976 (Box 532)